



# **Mohd Meraj Ansari**

**Date of birth:** 03/11/1997 | **Nationality:** Indian | **Gender:** Male | **Phone number:** 

(+91) 9453920714 (Mobile) | **Email address:** <u>bcameraj007@gmail.com</u> | **LinkedIn:** 

https://shorturl.at/suOTY | WhatsApp Messenger: +919453920714 |

**Address:** Govind bagh, 271201, Balrampur, India (Home)

#### ABOUT ME

I am a Graduate in computer science enrolled in Bachelor of computer applications from Avadh University's affiliated college MLK PG college Balrampur. I worked as a Data entry operator at Abdallah Al-Othaim markets company in Saudi Arabia from 28/08/2019 to 18/04/2024.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

28/08/2019 - 18/04/2024 Riyadh, Saudi Arabia

## DATA ENTRY CLERK ABDULLAH AL OTHAIM MARKETS COMPANY

- · Receiving invoices.
- · Collecting data, reviewing and manipulating.
- Goods receiving in warehouse operations.
- · Minor system and technical failures.
- To ensure that all the systems and devices are working properly in the branch.
- Verifying, reviewing databases and document control.
- Implementing data security and management policies.
- Responding to requests for data.
- · Maintaining confidentiality.
- · Performing data backups.

01/05/2013 - 31/10/2013 Balrampur, India

# **DATA ENTRY CLERK PATHIK HOTEL AND RESIDENCE**

- Maintenance and management of computers.
- Relationship with customers.
- · Handling cashflow.
- Generate reports and store outputs in the database.
- Compare data from different sources for administrative purposes.
- Assist with other tasks, such as processing invoices or order returns

01/03/2014 - 30/06/2014 Balrampur, India

# **COMPUTER OPERATOR CITY CYBER CAFE**

- Enter commands and thus start operations.
- Perform troubleshooting for various system errors.
- Configuring desktops and other hardware components.
- Resolves customer requests and questions.
- Addressing equipment malfunctions and software problems.

# EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/07/2014 - 30/04/2017 Faizabad, India

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS Dr Ram Manohar Lohia Avadh University

Website www.rmlau.ac.in

01/11/2013 - 28/02/2014 Balrampur, India

## **COURSE ON COMPUTER CONCEPTS** National Institute of Electronics and Information Technology

Website www.nielit.gov.in

01/07/2011 - 30/04/2013 Balrampur, India

HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATION City Montessori Inter College Balrampur

Website www.ccmsmb

01/07/2009 - 30/04/2011 Balrampur, India

SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATION City Montessori Inter College Balrampur

Website www.ccmsmb

01/07/2024 - 15/07/2024 Balrampur, India

**PYTHON FUNDAMENTALS** Great learning

Website <a href="https://www.mygreatlearning.com">https://www.mygreatlearning.com</a> | Level in EQF EQF level 6

16/07/2024 - 31/07/2024 Balrampur, India

**MYSQL BASICS** Great learning

Website <a href="https://www.mygreatlearning.com">https://www.mygreatlearning.com</a> | Level in EQF EQF level 6

01/08/2024 - 10/08/2024 Balrampur, India

**DATA VISUALIZATION WITH POWER BI** Great learning

Website <a href="https://www.mygreatlearning.com">https://www.mygreatlearning.com</a> | Level in EQF EQF level 6

01/09/2024 - CURRENT

**FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP** Udemy

Website www.Udemy.com

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **HINDI** 

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production Spoken interaction		
ENGLISH	C1	C2	C1	C1	B2
ARABIC	A2	A2	B1	B1	A2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

## DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft word | Microsoft PowerPoint | Data entry | Computer operator | Outlook | Skype | Google drive | Microsofe Excel | Pyhon programming language | Basic Knowlege of PHP/MySQL | Begginer HTML/CSS | Data Entry & Organization of Data | Microsoft Power-BI

## HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Watching and playing football

Watching stand up comedy

Visiting to ancient monuments

**Reading historic scriptures**